A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.3-SG 1.8 (A76-A82) FA209
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects (A82), 1944-2002; 8; 164.55 Cubic Feet Boxes 1077-1506. 392 letter-sized boxes, 24 legal-sized boxes, 6 half-letter-sized boxes, 6 half-legal-sized boxes, one 21x17 short oversized box, one 18x14 short oversized box, and 3 containers; Document boxes 1077-1506.
  - United States, 200; 76.96 Cubic Feet 202 containers
    - State University of New York at Buffalo - Environmental Perception, 1975-1980 (Box 1255, Folder 8473-8475, Box 1256, Folder 8476-8477)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo - Environmental Perception - Evaluation, 1976-1980 (Box 1256, Folder 8478)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo - Environmental Perception - Supplementary Material, 1974-1977 (Box 1256, Folder 8479-8480)
    - State University of New York at Stony Brook - Urban Careers, 1971-1980, 1982 (Box 1256, Folder 8481, Box 1257, Folder 8482-8483)
    - State University of New York at Stony Brook - Urban Careers - Evaluation, 1972-1980 (Box 1257, Folder 8484)
    - State University of New York at Stony Brook - Urban Careers - Supplemetary Material, 1972-1974 (Box 1257, Folder 8485)
    - State University of New York at Stony Brook - Water Pollution, 1974-1982 (Box 1257, Folder 8486-8489)
    - State University of New York at Stony Brook - Water Pollution - Evaluation, 1976-1981 (Box 1258, Folder 8490)
    - State University of New York at Stony Brook - Water Pollution - Supplementary Material, 1978 (Box 1258, Folder 8491)
    - Tannewald, R., 1979 May 24 (Box 1258, Folder 8492)
    - United Nations Association of the U.S.A, Inc., 1978-1980, 1982 (Box 1258, Folder 8493)
    - University of Chicago - School Superintendency Analysis, 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1258, Folder 8494)
    - University of Chicago - School Superintendency Analysis - Evaluation, 1977-1980 (Box 1258, Folder 8495)
    - University of Denver - Center of Policy Impacts, 1975-1978, 1980, 1982 (Box 1258, Folder 8496-8497, Box 1259, Folder 8498-8500)
    - University of Denver - Center of Policy Impacts - Evaluation, 1976-1980 (Box 1259, Folder 8501)
    - University of Denver - Center of Policy Impacts - Supplementary Material, 1977-1978 (Box 1259, Folder 8502-8503, Box 1260, Folder 8504)
    - University of Florida - Wetlands Management, 1972-1985 (Box 1260, Folder 8505-8509, Box 1261, Folder 8510-8511)
    - University of Florida - Wetlands Management - Evaluation, 1973-1980 (Box 1261, Folder 8512)
    - University of Florida - Wetlands Management - Supplementary Material, 1971-1984 (Box 1261, Folder 8513-8515, Box 1262, Folder 8516-8517, Box 1263, Folder 8518-8521, Box 1264, Folder 8522-8525, Box 1265, Folder 8526-8528, Box 1266, Folder 8529-8530)
    - University of Miami - Management Internship, 1971-1982 (Box 1266, Folder 8531, Box 1267, Folder 8532)
    - University of Miami - Management Internship - Supplementary Material, 1976 (Box 1267, Folder 8533)
    - University of Michigan - Global CO₂, 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1267, Folder 8534)
    - University of Michigan - Global CO₂ - Evaluation, 1978-1980 (Box 1267, Folder 8535)
    - University of North Carolina - Black Press, 1975-1980, 1982 (Box 1267, Folder 8536-8538, Box 1268, Folder 8539)
    - University of North Carolina - Black Press - Evaluation, 1977-1981, 1983 (Box 1268, Folder 8540)
    - University of North Carolina - Black Press - Supplementary Material, 1979-1980 (Box 1268, Folder 8541)
    - University of North Carolina - Infant Mortality, 1979-1982 (Box 1268, Folder 8542)
    - University of North Carolina - Stone, 1976-1982 (Box 1268, Folder 8543)
    - University of North Carolina - Stone - Evaluation, 1977-1981 (Box 1268, Folder 8544)
    - University of Notre Dame, 1978-1980, 1982 (Box 1268, Folder 8545)
    - University of Notre Dame - Civil Rights Study, 1978-1983, 1985 (Box 1268, Folder 8546-8547)
    - University of Washington - Biogeochemical Cycles, 1977-1982 (Box 1269, Folder 8548)
    - University of Washington - Biogeochemical Cycles - Evaluation, 1978 (Box 1269, Folder 8549)
    - University of Washington - Insect Control, 1973-1982 (Box 1269, Folder 8550-8553)
    - University of Washington - Insect Control - Evaluation, 1973-1981 (Box 1269, Folder 8554)
    - University of Washington - Insect Control - Supplementary Material, 1975, 1978, 1980 (Box 1269, Folder 8555)
    - Urban Coalition - Urban Schools, 1978-1982 (Box 1270, Folder 8556)
    - Urban Coalition - Urban Schools - Evaluation, 1978-1981 (Box 1270, Folder 8557)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute - Students Assistance, 1965-1979, 1980, 1982 (Box 1270, Folder 8558)
    - Wake Forest University - Television Series, 1976-1980, 1982 (Box 1270, Folder 8559)
    - Wake Forest University - Television Series, 1977-1978 (Box 1270, Folder 8560)
    - Wake Forest University - Television Series - Evaluation, 1977-1980 (Box 1270, Folder 8561)
    - Wake Forest University - Television Series - Supplementary Material, 1977 Aug. (Box 1270, Folder 8562)
    - Wake Forest University - Television Series - Supplementary Material, 1975, 1977 (Box 1271, Folder 8563)
    - West Virginia University - Rural Poverty, 1968-1980, 1982 (Box 1271, Folder 8564-8568, Box 1272, Folder 8569-8573, Box 1273, Folder 8574-8576)
    - West Virginia University - Rural Poverty - Evaluation, 1968-1980 (Box 1273, Folder 8577)
    - West Virginia University - Rural Poverty - Supplementary Material, 1959-1980 (Box 1273, Folder 8578-8579, Box 1274, Folder 8580-8585, Box 1275, Folder 8586-8590)
    - Wilberforce University - Lyle, 1976-1980, 1982 (Box 1275, Folder 8591)
    - Wilberforce University - Lyle - Evaluation, 1977-1980 (Box 1275, Folder 8592)
    - Winston-Salem State University - Staff Training, 1977-1982 (Box 1275, Folder 8593)
    - Winston-Salem State University - Staff Training - Evaluation, 1977-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 1276, Folder 8594)
    - Work in America Institute, Inc. - Urban Youth Jobs, 1976-1980, 1982 (Box 1276, Folder 8595-8599)
    - Work in America Institute, Inc. - Urban Youth Jobs - Evaluation, 1978-1980 (Box 1276, Folder 8600)
    - Work in America Institute, Inc. - Urban Youth Jobs - Supplementary Material, 1979 (Box 1277, Folder 8601-8602)
    - Yale University - Forest Ecosystems, 1975-1980 (Box 1277, Folder 8603)
    - Yale University - Forest Ecosystems - Evaluation, 1975-1980 (Box 1277, Folder 8604)
    - Yale University - Forest Ecosystems - Supplementary Material, 1976-1979 (Box 1277, Folder 8605-8606)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, A
      - Baylor College of Medicine - Garza, 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1278, Folder 8607)
      - Baylor College of Medicine - Garza - Evaluation, 1977-1980 (Box 1278, Folder 8608)
      - Baylor College of Medicine - Implantation Symposium, 1978-1982 (Box 1278, Folder 8609)
      - Colorado State University - Reproductive Physiology, 1972-1982 (Box 1278, Folder 8610-8613)
      - Colorado State University - Reproductive Physiology - Evaluation, 1973-1980 (Box 1278, Folder 8614)
      - Colorado State University - Reproductive Physiology - Supplementary Material, 1975-1980 (Box 1279, Folder 8615-8616)
      - Columbia University - Population Encyclopedia, 1978-1980 (Box 1279, Folder 8617)
      - Columbia University - Population Encyclopedia - Evaluation, 1978-1981 (Box 1279, Folder 8618)
      - Cornell University - Gibbs, 1976-1980, 1982 (Box 1279, Folder 8619)
      - Cornell University - Gibbs - Evaluation, 1976-1981 (Box 1279, Folder 8620)
      - Cornell University - Gonadotropin Analogues & Blastocyst Development, 1977-1980, 1982, 1984 (Box 1279, Folder 8621)
      - Harvard University - Briscoe, 1978-1982 (Box 1279, Folder 8622)
      - Harvard University - Briscoe - Evaluation, 1978-1980 (Box 1279, Folder 8623)
      - Harvard University - Health Policy in Developed Countries, 1978-1982 (Box 1280, Folder 8624)
      - Harvard University - Health Policy in Developed Countries - Evaluation, 1977-1979 (Box 1280, Folder 8625)
      - Howard University - Cell Biology Meeting, 1978-1980, 1982 (Box 1280, Folder 8626)
      - Howard University - Cell Biology Meeting - Evaluation, 1978-1980 (Box 1280, Folder 8627)
      - Lyle, Katherine Ch'iu, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 1280, Folder 8628)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Nutrition Program Analysis, 1977-1982 (Box 1280, Folder 8629)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Nutrition Program Analysis - Evaluation, 1977-1981 (Box 1280, Folder 8630)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Nutrition Program Analysis - Supplementary Material, 1981 (Box 1280, Folder 8631)
      - Michigan State University - Taeniasis, 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1280, Folder 8632)
      - Michigan State University - Taeniasis - Evaluation, 1977-1979 (Box 1280, Folder 8633)
      - National Academy of Sciences - Contraceptive Technology Symposium, 1977-1980, 1982 (Box 1280, Folder 8634)
      - National Academy of Sciences - Contraceptive Technology Symposium - Evaluation, 1978-1980 (Box 1281, Folder 8635)
      - New York University - Female Reproduction, 1979-1982 (Box 1281, Folder 8636)
      - Population Council - Summer Employment for Minorities, 1978-1980, 1982 (Box 1281, Folder 8637)
      - Population Council - Summer Employment for Minorities - Evaluation, 1978-1979, 1982 (Box 1281, Folder 8638)
      - Projects for Population Action, 1975-1982 (Box 1281, Folder 8639-8642)
      - Projects for Population Action - Evaluation, 1976-1977, 1979-1980 (Box 1281, Folder 8643)
      - Projects for Population Action - Supplementary Material, 1975, 1977-1978 (Box 1282, Folder 8644-8645)
      - Salk Institute for Biological Studies - Reproductive Biology, 1969-1982 (Box 1282, Folder 8646-8650, Box 1283, Folder 8651-8653)
      - Salk Institute for Biological Studies - Reproductive Biology - Supplementary Material, 1972-1977 (Box 1283, Folder 8654-8656, Box 1284, Folder 8657-8660)
      - Seidel, George E., 1978-1980, 1982 (Box 1284, Folder 8661)
      - Seidel, George E. - Evaluation, 1978-1980 (Box 1284, Folder 8662)
      - University of Idaho - Reproductive Biology, 1978-1983 (Box 1284, Folder 8663)
      - University of Idaho - Reproductive Biology - Evaluation, 1978 (Box 1284, Folder 8664)
      - Washington University - Urology, 1975-1980, 1982 (Box 1284, Folder 8665)
      - Washington University - Urology - Evaluation, 1976-1978, 1985, 1987 (Box 1284, Folder 8666)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Brandeis University - International Food Corps, 1976-1982, 1987 (Box 1285, Folder 8667-8668)
      - Brandeis University - International Food Corps - Evaluation, 1977-1981, 1983 (Box 1285, Folder 8669)
      - Harvard University - Insect Control, 1973-1974, 1980-1982, 1986 (Box 1285, Folder 8670)
      - Iowa State University - Maize, 1976-1982 (Box 1285, Folder 8671)
      - Iowa State University - Maize - Evaluation, 1977-1981, 1983 (Box 1285, Folder 8672)
      - National Academy of Sciences - Scientists Exchange, 1978-1982 (Box 1285, Folder 8673)
      - New York University - Trypanosomiasis, 1976-1980, 1982 (Box 1286, Folder 8674)
      - New York University - Trypanosomiasis - Evaluation, 1976-1979 (Box 1286, Folder 8675)
      - Ohio State University - Malaria and Babesiosis Conference, 1977-1982 (Box 1286, Folder 8676-8679)
      - Ohio State University - Malaria and Babesiosis Conference - Evaluation, 1978-1981 (Box 1286, Folder 8680)
      - Ohio State University - Malaria and Babesiosis Conference - Supplementary Material, 1976-1979 (Box 1287, Folder 8681)
      - Oregon State University - Triticale, 1976-1980, 1982 (Box 1287, Folder 8682)
      - Oregon State University - Triticale - Evaluation, 1976-1979 (Box 1287, Folder 8683)
      - Pennsylvania State University - Plant Disease, 1977-1982 (Box 1287, Folder 8684)
      - Pennsylvania State University - Plant Disease - Evaluation, 1977-1981, 1983 (Box 1287, Folder 8685)
      - Rockefeller University - Trypanosomiasis, 1973-1980, 1982 (Box 1287, Folder 8686)
      - Rockefeller University - Trypanosomiasis - Evaluation, 1973-1979 (Box 1287, Folder 8687)
      - Rockefeller University - Trypanosomiasis - Supplementary Material, 1977 (Box 1287, Folder 8688)
      - Southern Regional Education Board, 1975-1981 (Box 1288, Folder 8689)
      - Southern Regional Education Board - Evaluation, 1975-1978, 1980, 1982-1983 (Box 1288, Folder 8690)
      - University of California - Germplasm, Davis, 1978-1983 (Box 1288, Folder 8691)
      - University of Florida - Peanuts, 1973-1982 (Box 1288, Folder 8692-8694)
      - University of Florida - Peanuts - Evaluation, 1975-1980 (Box 1288, Folder 8695)
      - University of Florida - Peanuts - Supplementary Material, 1974-1975 (Box 1288, Folder 8696)
      - University of Florida - Peanuts - Supplementary Material, 1978 (Box 1289, Folder 8697)
      - University of Hawaii - Bibliographic Service, 1978-1980, 1982 (Box 1289, Folder 8698)
      - University of Hawaii - Evaluation, 1978-1980 (Box 1289, Folder 8699)
      - University of Idaho - Oocyte Growth, 1978-1982 (Box 1289, Folder 8700)
      - University of Iowa - Cockroach, 1978-1980, 1982, 1986 (Box 1289, Folder 8701)
      - University of Minnesota - Frost Resistance, 1968-1982 (Box 1289, Folder 8702, Box 1290, Folder 8703-8707)
      - University of Minnesota - Frost Resistance - Supplementary Material, 1971-1973 (Box 1291, Folder 8708)
      - University of Minnesota - Frost Resistance - Supplementary Material - Book - "Plant Cold Hardiness and Freezing Stress", 1978 (Box 1291, Folder 8709)
      - University of Wisconsin - Food Policy Seminar, 1978-1982 (Box 1291, Folder 8710)
      - University of Wisconsin - Giwa, 1978-1982 (Box 1291, Folder 8711)
      - Washington State University - Dry Beans, 1978-1982 (Box 1291, Folder 8712)
      - Washington State University - Evaluation, 1977-1980 (Box 1291, Folder 8713)
      - Washington State University - Supplementary Material, 1976-1979 (Box 1291, Folder 8714, Box 1292, Folder 8715)
      - White, Jeffrey W., 1978-1983 (Box 1292, Folder 8716)
      - White, Jeffrey W. - Supplementary Material, 1980 Jan. 8 (Box 1292, Folder 8717)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Bruni, John Frederick, 1978-1980, 1982 (Box 1292, Folder 8718)
      - Bruni, John Frederick - Closed, 1978-1980 (Box 1292, Folder 8718A)
        Conditions Governing Access
        Restricted - Confidential material - Folder removed from Box 1292
      - Caldwell, John Stephen, 1977-1982 (Box 1292, Folder 8719)
      - Caldwell, John Stephen - Closed, 1978-1980 (Box 1292, Folder 8719A)
      - Caldwell, John Stephen, 1979-1981 (Box 1293, Folder 8720)
      - Caldwell, John Stephen photos, 1979 Oct. 29 (Box 1293, Folder 8720A)
        Photos removed from Box 1293 - Housed in separate box at end of RG1.8
      - Cohen, Steven A., 1978-1980, 1982 (Box 1293, Folder 8721)
      - Cohen, Steven A. - Closed, 1977-1978 (Box 1293, Folder 8721A)
        Restricted - Confidential material - Folder removed from Box 1293
      - Cohen, Steven A. - Supplementary Material, 1976 August, 1977 (Box 1293, Folder 8722-8723)
      - Emerich, David William, 1976-1980, 1982 (Box 1293, Folder 8724)
      - Emerich, David William - Closed, 1976-1979 (Box 1293, Folder 8724A)
      - Emerich, David William, 1978-1979 (Box 1293, Folder 8725)
      - Frederickson, Mary Evans (Box 1294, Folder 8726)
      - Glabe, C. G. (Box 1294, Folder 8727)
      - Haugland, Richard Alan (Box 1294, Folder 8728)
      - Janiewski, Dolores E. (Box 1294, Folder 8729)
      - Kelsoe, Garnette Herrel (Box 1294, Folder 8730)
      - Kenmore, Peter E. (Box 1294, Folder 8731)
      - Kinsey, William Henderson (Box 1295, Folder 8732)
      - Klessig, Daniel Frederick (Box 1295, Folder 8733)
      - Levine, Joel Martin (Box 1295, Folder 8734)
      - Lopo, Alina (Box 1295, Folder 8735)
      - Ludwig, Robert Allen (Box 1295, Folder 8736)
      - Matthews, David Earl (Box 1295, Folder 8737)
      - Meltzoff, Sarah Keene (Box 1295, Folder 8738, Box 1296, Folder 8739)
      - Miller, Stephan Sherman (Box 1296, Folder 8740)
      - Ritterbush, Stephen W. (Box 1296, Folder 8741)
      - Sacks, David Lawrence (Box 1296, Folder 8742)
      - Schackmann, Robert Wayne (Box 1297, Folder 8743)
      - Tilton, Varien Russell (Box 1297, Folder 8744)
      - Wilkes, Mahlon McGregor (Box 1297, Folder 8745)
      - Young-Day, Kay (Box 1297, Folder 8746-8748)
    - United States - Population Sciences, P
      - Philadelphia College of Pharmacy & Science - Embryonic Cell Workshop (Box 1298, Folder 8749)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, R
      - Alice Lloyd College - Photographic Archives (Box 1298, Folder 8750-8756)
      - American Academy of Arts & Sciences - "Love & Work in Adulthood - Workshop (Box 1299, Folder 8757-8759)
      - American Center for Students & Artists (Box 1299, Folder 8760-8762)
      - American Center for Students & Artists - Spring Festival, 1979 (Box 1299, Folder 8763)
      - American Conservatory Theatre - American Plays (Box 1299, Folder 8764-8765)
      - American Council of Learned Societies - Preparatory Fellowships (Box 1300, Folder 8766-8771, Box 1301, Folder 8772-8774)
      - American Dance Festival - Dance Television Workshop (Box 1301, Folder 8775-8776)
      - American Film Institute - Film-Making Workshop for Humanists (Box 1301, Folder 8777-8779, Box 1302, Folder 8780)
      - American Historical Association - Historical Sciences Conference (Box 1302, Folder 8781-8785)
        Folder 8781 (I); Folders 8782-8784 (II); Folder 8785 (Evaluation)
      - American Historical Association - Historical Sciences Conference: Supplementary Material (Box 1302, Folder 8786)
      - American Humanist Association - Television Series, 1975-1981 (Box 1303, Folder 8787-8788)
        Folder 8788 (Evaluation)
      - American Humanist Association - Television Series: Supplementary Material (Box 1303, Folder 8789)
      - American Hungarian Foundation - Edmund Vasvary Collection, 1974-1981 (Box 1303, Folder 8790-8792)
        Folder 8790 (I), Folder 8791 (II), Folder 8792 (Evaluation)
      - American Hungarian Foundation - Edmund Vasvary Collection: Supplementary Material (Box 1303, Folder 8793)
      - American Shakespeare Festival - Audience Development, 1977-1979 (Box 1303, Folder 8794-8795)
        Folder 8795 (Evaluation)
      - American Universities Field Staff - Culture & Education Systems, 1974-1981 (Box 1303, Folder 8796-8797, Box 1304, Folder 8798-8799)
        Folder 8796 (I), Folders 8797-8798 (II), Folder 8799 (Evaluation)
      - American Universities Field Staff - Culture & Education Systems: Supplementary Material (Box 1304, Folder 8800)
      - Arkansas Consumer Research - Desmarais, Ralph H., 1975-1979 (Box 1304, Folder 8801-8802)
        Folder 8802 (Evaluation)
      - Art News Archive Foundation, 1974-1981 (Box 1304, Folder 8803-8805)
        Folder 8803 (I), Folder 8804 (II), Folder 8805 (Evaluation)
      - Aspen Institute - Einstein Symposium, 1977-1982 (Box 1304, Folder 8806, Box 1305, Folder 8807)
      - Atlas Theatre Company, Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 1305, Folder 8808-8809)
        Folder 8809 (Evaluation)
      - Barnard College - Women's Programs Conference, 1977-1980 (Box 1305, Folder 8810-8811)
        Folder 8811 (Evaluation)
      - Barnard College - Women's Programs Conference: Supplementary Material (Box 1305, Folder 8812)
      - Barron, Ros, 1977-1980 (Box 1305, Folder 8813-8814)
        Folder 8814 (Evaluation)
      - Bay Area Video Coalition, Inc. - Pilot Program, 1977-1980 (Box 1305, Folder 8815-8816)
        Folder 8816 (Evaluation)
      - Berman, Ronald S., 1978-1980 (Box 1305, Folder 8817)
      - Black Theatre Alliance - New Space, 1977-1981 (Box 1305, Folder 8818, Box 1306, Folder 8819-8820)
        Folder 8820 (Evaluation)
      - Boston University - Papanek, Hanna, 1974-1980 (Box 1306, Folder 8821-8823)
        Folder 8821 (I), Folder 8822 (II), Folder 8823 (Evaluation)
      - Boston University - Papanek, Hanna: Supplementary Material (Box 1306, Folder 8824)
      - Bowes, Ed, 1977-1981 (Box 1306, Folder 8825)
      - Brandeis University - History of Public Policy Conference, 1978-1980 (Box 1306, Folder 8826-8827)
        Folder 8827 (Evaluation)
      - Burgess, David Lowry, 1978-1981 (Box 1306, Folder 8828, Box 1307, Folder 8829)
      - Burgess, David Lowry: Supplementary Material (Box 1307, Folder 8830)
      - Cable Arts Foundation, Inc., 1977-1979, 1981-1983 (Box 1307, Folder 8831-8832)
        Folder 8832 (Evaluation)
      - Cable Arts Foundation, Inc. - Group Portrait Program, 1978-1979, 1981 (Box 1307, Folder 8833-8834)
        Folder 8834 (Evaluation)
      - Cable Arts Foundation, Inc. - Television Promotion, 1977-1978 (Box 1307, Folder 8835-8836)
        Folder 8836 (Evaluation)
      - Carnegie-Mellon University - Policy Studies and Humanities Research, 1976-1981 (Box 1307, Folder 8837-8838, Box 1308, Folder 8839)
        Folder 8839 (Evaluation)
      - Carter, Janette, 1976-1979, 1981 (Box 1308, Folder 8840-8842)
        Folder 8842 (Evaluation)
      - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences - Humanities Fellowships, 1976-1980 (Box 1308, Folder 8843-8844)
        Folder 8844 (Evaluation)
      - Center for Southern Folklore - Multimedia, 1973-1981, 1988 (Box 1308, Folder 8845, Box 1309, Folder 8846-8850, Box 1310, Folder 8851)
        Folder 8851 (Evaluation)
      - Center for Southern Folklore - Multimedia: Supplementary Material (Box 1310, Folder 8852-8855, Box 1311, Folder 8856-8858)
      - Center for Southern Folklore - Multimedia: Supplementary Material (Box T1)
        Long Playing Record: "Ray Lum: Mule Trader"; produced by Center for Southern Folklore; Bill Ferris, Judy Peiser, Directors; June 1977. Originally part of Multi-Media Package which included the record album and two booklets
        Open for research. Digital access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
      - Center for Theatre Practice, Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 1311, Folder 8859-8861)
        Folder 8861 (Evaluation)
      - City University of New York Graduate School - Contemporary Citizenship Conference, 1978-1980 (Box 1312, Folder 8862)
      - City University of New York Graduate School - Contemporary Citizenship Conference: Supplementary Material (Box 1312, Folder 8863)
      - Clarke, Martha, 1978-1981 (Box 1312, Folder 8864)
      - Columbia University - Expressive Behavior Study, 1975-1982, 1984, 1986-1987 (Box 1312, Folder 8865-8866)
      - Columbia University - Expressive Behavior Study: Supplementary Material (Box 1312, Folder 8867, Box 1313, Folder 8868-8869)
      - Columbia University - Expressive Behavior Study: Supplementary Material (Box T1)
        Audio cassette: "Grass Roots, An Oral History of the American People; An Audio Cassette Program from Visual Education Corporation; ©1976; Northeast (cassette 5421-01)
      - Columbia University - Expressive Behavior Study: Supplementary Material (Box T1)
        Audio cassette: "Grass Roots, An Oral History of the American People; An Audio Cassette Program from Visual Education Corporation; ©1976; South (cassette 5421-02)
      - Columbia University - Expressive Behavior Study: Supplementary Material (Box T1)
        Audio cassette: "Grass Roots, An Oral History of the American People; An Audio Cassette Program from Visual Education Corporation; ©1976; Midwest (cassette 5421-03)
      - Columbia University - Expressive Behavior Study: Supplementary Material (Box T1)
        Audio cassette: "Grass Roots, An Oral History of the American People; An Audio Cassette Program from Visual Education Corporation; ©1976; Southwest (cassette 5421-04)
      - Columbia University - Expressive Behavior Study: Supplementary Material (Box T1)